# YAZMIN MORAN

#### **BUSINESS STUDENT**

#### CONTACT

224 509 4896 Yazminmoran1128@gmail.com 105 Birch St. Carpentersville, IL, 60110

## **SKILLS**

Bilingual (Eng/Span)
Communication
Leadership Role

#### **EDUCATION**

2018-2022 High School Diploma, General Education

Barrington High School

William Rainey Harper College

2024-present

Associate in arts

Business/ Entrepreneurship

#### **PROFILE**

I am currently a first-year college student studying business



with a special interest in social media, although I don't have experience in a business job, I am a very quick learner and hope to find a job that will allow me to grow my skills needed for when I graduate.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

<u>Head machine operator</u> – Claires Corporate Headquarters

## 2023-present

- Close boxes/ ship to store with handheld scanner
- Activate/ close out carts with RF scanner
- Print shipping labels
- Recount merchandise/print out new sheet
- Maintain area clean / organized

## K.E.E.P Site supervisor – Barrington Park District

## 2021-2023

- Organize/ hand out snack
- Take attendance
- Sign out
- Stay in contact with parents to update them
- Plan / lead activities

### Assistant Teacher - Palatine KinderCare

## 2023-2023

- Check in children at arrival
- Monitor last meal / nap
- Update parent's hourly with pictures
- Set up / hand out food during lunch
- Report incident when occurred